听力考试正式开始，请看听力部分第一节。
第一节，听下面五段对话，
每段对话后有一。
个小题：从题中所给的
三个选项中，选出最佳选项，并标在试卷的相应位置。
听完每段对话后，你都有十秒钟的时间来。
来回答有关小题和阅读下一小题。
每段对话仅读一遍。
例如，现在你有五秒钟的时间看试卷上的例题。
你将听到以下内容。
你将有五秒钟的时。
之间，将正确答案标在试卷上。
衬衫的价格为九磅十五便士，
所以你选择
项，并将其标在试卷上。
现在。你有五秒钟的时间
阅读第一小题的有关内容。
Professor Jackson, could I talk to you about my paper sometime today?
Sure. When the class is over, I need to go to the lab first, and then I'll be at the
cafeteria at about 1230.
Let's meet there.
Okay. Thanks, Professor Jackson.
What are you cooking?
It smells delicious!
I'm making a carrot cake.
Nice! I see a roast chicken and an apple pie over there, too.
The chicken is for dinner, and the pie is for Jeff.
He has to take something to school tomorrow.
This neighborhood really needs a library.
How can we get one?
I think we should have a meeting to talk about it.
Hi, Jim. How's your new job going?
It's very exciting, and I'm really learning a lot.
But it's also quite tiring.
I feel like a good break this weekend.
Amanda, what skill would you like to develop?
Well, I want to learn to play the guitar.
I love writing songs, you and I think it would be lovely if I could play my own
music and entertain people.
第一节到此结束。
第二节。
2 After reading.
听下面五段对话或独白。
每段对话或独白后有几个小题，
从题中所给的
三个选项中，选出最佳选项，并标在。试卷的相应位置。
听每段对话或独白前，
你将有时间阅读各个小题。
每小题五秒钟。
听完后，各小题将给出五秒钟。
的作答时间。
每段对话或独白，读两遍。
听下面一段对话，回答
第六和第七两个小题。
现在你有十秒。
小钟的时间，阅读这两个小题。
Hello? City Bank?
Can I help you?
Hi. I'm calling for information on opening a savings account.
Have you had any accounts in our bank before?
No, I don't think so.
Then you'll have to go in person to one of our branches and talk to a clerk there.
I see. Is there a near Brown College?
We have one branch at 135 Dudley Road and one at 512 Kingfield Street.
I think I will go to the one on Dudley.
Thank you. Hello?
City Bank? Can I help you?
Hi. I'm calling for information on opening a savings account.
Have you had any accounts in our bank before?
No, I don't think so.
Then you'll have to go in person to one of our branches and talk to a there.
I see. Is there a bank near Brown College?
We have one branch at 135 Dudley Road and one at 512 Kingfield Street.
I think I will go to the one on Dudley.
Thank you. Thank you.
听下面一段对话，回答
Answer Answer the following questions from read questions 8th 10th.
第八至第十三个小题。
现在，你有十五秒钟的时间
阅读这三个小题。
Good morning. Frank Sampson's.
Good morning. This is Peter Clifford from Smart Tech.
Could I speak to Mr.
Smith, please? I'm sorry.
Mr. Smith is having a meeting right now.
Would you like to leave a message or call back later?
time is the meeting over?
Well, it started at one o and it usually lasts about two hours.
All right. In that case, could you please tell him to check his email?
I've sent him an important document.
I'm waiting for his reply.
Certainly. Anything else, sir?
Yes. I'd like to know what will be the best time for us to meet before Friday.
I must meet him this week.
Please tell him to include the time in his reply.
Do you want to meet him in our office or in your office, sir?
Oh, either is fine.
All right, sir.
I'll tell him when he's back.
Good morning. Frank Sampson's.
Good morning. This is Peter Clifford from Smart Tech.
Could I speak to Mr.
Smith, please? I'm sorry.
Mr. Smith is having a meeting right now.
Would you like to leave a message or call back later?
What time is the meeting over?
Well, it started at one o and it usually lasts about two hours.
All right. In that case, could you please tell him to check his email?
I've sent him an important document.
I'm waiting for his reply.
Certainly. Anything else, sir?
Yes. I'd like to know what will be the best time for us to meet before Friday.
I must meet him this week.
Please tell him to include the time in his reply.
Do you want to meet him in our office or in your office, sir?
Oh, either is fine.
All right, sir.
I'll tell him when he's back.
you. Hi, Annie.
听下面一段对话。
回答第十一至第十三。
嗯，三个小题。
现在你有十五秒钟的时间
阅读这三个小题。
That's a very lovely bunch of It's for my sister.
It's her graduation day today.
It must have cost you a fortune.
I paid sixty dollars for it, but it's worth it.
Jane worked very hard for her degree over the last four years.
Today is a very important day for her and I want it to be special.
That's very nice of you.
I wish it were our graduation day, too.
Another three years, and we'll be done, too.
Where are they going to hold the graduation ceremony?
In the conference hall at 2 p.m.
It'll be a big ceremony.
I guess you should be there early.
Otherwise, you won't get a seat.
Yes, I'll try to find a seat close to the stage.
I want to take some good pictures of my sister.
Have fun, Give Jane my best wishes.
Thanks. Bye, Steve.
Hi, Annie. That's a lovely bunch of It's for my sister.
It's her graduation day today.
It must have cost you a fortune.
I paid sixty dollars for it, but it's worth it.
Jane worked very hard for her degree over the last four years.
Today is a very important day for her and I want it to be special.
That's very nice of you.
I wish it were our graduation day, too.
Another three years, and we'll be done, too.
Where are they going to hold the graduation ceremony?
In the conference hall at 2 p.m.
It'll be a big ceremony.
I guess you should be there early.
Otherwise, you won't get a seat.
Yes, I'll try to find a seat close to the stage.
I want to take some good pictures of my sister.
Have fun, Give Jane my best wishes.
Thanks. Bye, Steve.
听下面一段对话，回答
第十四至第十七四个小题。
现在。哎，你有二十秒钟的时间
阅读这四个小题。
Oh, I can't believe it.
Peter, I haven't seen you for ages.
How are you?
Hi, Laura. Nice to meet you here.
I'm pretty good.
How about you?
I'm fine. It's really great to see you.
Do you have time to sit down?
I was leaving, but I can join you for a few minutes.
Great. So tell me, how's your family?
Well, it keeps getting bigger.
We have four kids now.
All boys. Four boys?
I suppose they keep you busy.
They sure do.
The baby is only one month old, so Sally is not working right now.
And what's new with you and Believe it or not, he's home with the kids.
You're kidding. No, I'm not.
Jim chose to work from home so we could spend less on childcare.
I love it because he does all the shopping and cleaning.
Good point. Yikes!
It's already 12.30.
I have to go now.
I have an important meeting this afternoon.
Tell Jim I said hi, and I'll call you so we can have dinner sometime.
Great. And say hi to Sally and the kids.
See you. See you.
Oh, I can't believe it.
Peter, I haven't seen you for ages.
How are you?
Hi, Laura. Nice to meet you here.
I'm pretty good.
How about you?
I'm fine. It's really great to see you.
Do you have time to sit down?
I was leaving, but I can join you for a few minutes.
Great. So tell me, how's your family?
Well, it keeps getting bigger.
We have four kids now.
All boys. Four boys?
I suppose they keep you busy.
They sure do.
The baby is only one month old, so Sally is not working right now.
And what's new with you and Jim?
Believe it or not, he's home with the kids.
You're kidding. No, I'm not.
Jim chose to work from home so we could spend less on childcare.
I love it because he does all the shopping and cleaning.
Good point. Yikes!
It's already 12.30.
I have to go now.
I have an important meeting this afternoon.
Tell Jim I said hi, and I'll call you so we can have dinner sometime.
Great. And say hi to Sally and the kids.
See you. See you.
听下面一段独白。
回答第十八至第二十三个小题。
现在你有十五秒钟的时间
阅读这三个小题。
Good evening, everyone.
I'm Jennifer Green.
Thanks for joining us.
In today's edition of Perfect Life, our guest is Brock Bastian,
a social psychologist from the University of Melbourne.
Professor Bastian's research focuses on pain, happiness, and morality.
Recently, he published a book on the role of pain in promoting pleasure.
The title of the book is The Other Side of Happiness.
In this book, he argues that as we seek to escape pain or sorrow, are weakening
ourselves and may lose our adaptive ability to deal with pain in the future.
Painful experiences are in fact vital for our development and how we face the
unavoidable challenges ahead.
And they play a key role in helping us develop our ability to feel truly happy.
Now, let's welcome Professor Bastian to talk about his ideas in the book.
Good evening, everyone.
I'm Jennifer Green.
Thanks for joining us.
In today's edition of Perfect Life,
our guest is Brock Bastian,
a social psychologist from the University of Melbourne.
Bastian's research focuses on pain, happiness, and morality.
Recently, he published a book on the role of pain in promoting pleasure.
The title of the book is The Other Side of Happiness.
In this book, he argues that as we seek to escape pain or sorrow, we are weakening
ourselves and may lose our adaptive ability to deal with pain in the future.
Painful experiences are in fact vital for our development and how we face the
unavoidable challenges ahead.
And they play a key role in helping us develop our ability to feel truly happy.
Now, let's welcome Professor Bastian to talk about his ideas in the book.
In today's Life, our
第二节到此结束。
现在你有两分钟的时间，将试卷上的答案
on Thank you.
转涂到答题卡上。